## **Deniss Mijusovs**

Riga, Latvia | +371 23003848 | dmijusovs@gmail.com | LinkedIn Profile

#### JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### **PROFILE**

Junior Web developer. Self-learned experience in developing consumer-focused websites using **HTML**, **CSS**, and **JavaScript**. Already learned the **basics of React.js**. Able to write simple dynamic React.js web apps and constantly improve my skills. Good knowledge of best practices for web design, user experience, and speed. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting. Located in **Riga**, **Latvia**.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML/CSS	Styled components	MySQL/PostgreSQL
JavaScript ES6/ jQuery	Wordpress	ReactJS
Responsive Design /	PHP	Testing/Debugging
Bootstrap		

#### **PROJECTS**

Portfolio website: <a href="https://dmijusovs.great-site.net/">https://dmijusovs.great-site.net/</a>

React App - Expense tracker with filter by year and chart

Food order App - Food order app, cart, modal, total, add/remove item

#### **EDUCATION**

 $Bachelor\ of\ Engineering\ (BE)\ -\ Telecommunications.$ 

Riga Technical University (RTU) 2007 - 2010

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### IT - technical support (Webcast monitor at ON24) Contractor at Zest City supporting ON24 — Dec 2016 - Present (6 yrs 1 mos)

- Use the ON24 virtual product suite to set up webcasts, webinars, and virtual event elements such as registration pages, emails, content, locations, surveys, archives, and other event elements
- Coordinate with Event Managers to manage the delivery of key event-related elements
- Perform event-related tasks, such as conference bridge scheduling, work order processing, data input, answering event audience member inquiries, location design edits, and custom reports generation
- Work in a client-facing capacity to provide live webcast & virtual show monitoring and platform training
- Perform other webcast and virtual event-related activities as necessary

#### Logistics Management Specialist, Izoterms — Aug 2012 - Apr 2013 (9 mos)

- Ensuring orders are met on time. Deliveries of incoming and outgoing goods.
- Compliance with company health and safety and environmental policies and procedures.
- Ensuring that all materials are in accordance with established and authorised by management, with the correct specifications and at the lowest price related to quality.
- Creation/management of databases capable of monitoring all purchases activities related to the project from the investigation phase to dispatch and materials control.
- Work with the supply chain to develop logistics plans that meet the project needs.

# Customer Service Representative, Atea Global Services Ltd. — Mar 2012- May 2012(3 mos)

- Knowledge and experience of the installation and configuration of Microsoft operating systems and software.
- PC assembly and fault finding experience, network fundamentals.